const List<Map<String, dynamic>> FlutterWidgetsQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the `Text` widget in Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "A. To create buttons",
      "B. To display a string of text with a single style",
      "C. To arrange child widgets",
      "D. To display images"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. To display a string of text with a single style",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget is used to contain other widgets and apply styling, padding, and margins?",
    "options": [
      "A. Row",
      "B. Column",
      "C. Container",
      "D. Scaffold"
    ],
    "Answer": "C. Container",
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the `Column` widget arrange its children?",
    "options": [
      "A. Horizontally",
      "B. Vertically",
      "C. In a circular manner",
      "D. In a grid"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. Vertically",
  },
  {
    "question": "What can the `Image` widget display?",
    "options": [
      "A. Only images from the internet",
      "B. Only local asset images",
      "C. Both asset and network images",
      "D. Only animated images"
    ],
    "Answer": "C. Both asset and network images",
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an `ElevatedButton` in Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "A. A button that appears flat with no elevation",
      "B. A material button that is elevated when pressed",
      "C. A button that cannot be pressed",
      "D. A button that displays images only"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. A material button that is elevated when pressed",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget provides a framework for the structure of a Flutter app?",
    "options": [
      "A. Container",
      "B. Scaffold",
      "C. Column",
      "D. Row"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. Scaffold",
  },
  {
    "question": "How is a scrollable list of items created in Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "A. Using a GridView widget",
      "B. Using a ListView widget",
      "C. Using a Column widget",
      "D. Using a Stack widget"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. Using a ListView widget",
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the `TextFormField` widget?",
    "options": [
      "A. To display static text",
      "B. To validate user input",
      "C. To create a button",
      "D. To arrange widgets"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. To validate user input",
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you position child widgets inside a `Stack`?",
    "options": [
      "A. Using the Positioned widget",
      "B. Using the Align widget",
      "C. Using the Container widget",
      "D. Using the Column widget"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. Using the Positioned widget",
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the `GestureDetector` widget do?",
    "options": [
      "A. It detects gestures like taps, swipes, and long presses",
      "B. It creates a static container",
      "C. It arranges child widgets",
      "D. It displays images"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. It detects gestures like taps, swipes, and long presses",
  },
];
